# Herry

#### **Personal Information**

23/5 Watson Crescent Home Address:

Edinburgh, UK, EH11 1EZ

Date of Birth: March 13th, 1980

Email: herry13@gmail.com, h.herry@sms.ed.ac.uk

Homepage: http://homepages.inf.ed.ac.uk/s0978621

#### **Research Interests**

System Configuration, Automated Planning, Multi-agent System.

# PhD Research Project: Automated Planning for Cloud Service Configurations

Applying artificial intelligent planning techniques to solve problems in system configuration for managing cloud infrastructure by introducing automatic generation of workflows as well as autonomic and distributed workflow execution architecture.

#### **Educations**

# **Doctor of Philosophy**

School of Informatics, University of Edinburgh, UK

Funded by: HP Labs Innovation Research Program Award

### Master of Science (GPA: 3.86 of 4.00)

Faculty of Computer Science, University of Indonesia, Indonesia,

with 1-year visiting researcher at Imaging Science and Engineering,

Tokyo Institute of Technology, Japan

Thesis: Face Recognition System using Hough Transform

# Bachelor of Science (GPA: 3.52 of 4.00 - Cum Laude)

Faculty of Computer Science, University of Indonesia, Indonesia

Thesis: Performance of Optimised Probabilistic Neural Network based

on Genetic Algorithm in Odor Recognition System

# **Main Publications**

- P. Anderson and H. Herry, A Formal Semantics for the SmartFrog Configuration Language, 2014. (submitted)
- **H. Herry** and P. Anderson, *Planning Configuration Relocation on the BonFIRE Infrastructure*, CloudCom 2013 Workshop on Using and Building Cloud Testbeds (UNICO), Bristol, December 2013.
- H. Herry, P. Anderson, and M. Rovatsos, *Choreographing configuration changes*, the 9<sup>th</sup> International Conference on Network and Service Management (CNSM'13), Zurich, October 2013.
- P. Anderson, S. Bijani, and H. Herry, Multi-Agent Virtual Machine Management Using the Lightweight Coordination Calculus, Transactions on Computational Collective Intelligence XII, pages 123-142, 2013.
- H. Herry and P. Anderson, Planning with Global Constraints for Computing Infrastructure Reconfiguration, the AAAI-12 Workshop on Problem Solving using Classical Planners (CP4PS'12), Toronto, July 2012.
- **H. Herry**, P. Anderson, and G. Wickler, *Automated Planning for Configuration Changes*, the 25th Large Installation Systems Administration Conference (LISA'11), Boston, December 2011. (Best Student Paper)

#### **Other Publications**

W. Jatmiko, A. Wibowo, Abdurrahman S. K., Herry, A. A. Krisnadhi, A. Azurat, T. Fukuda, and K. Sekiyama, Self-Organizing Control of Urban Traffic Signal based on Multiway Intersection Offset-Setting Model, WSEAS Transactions on Systems and Control, Issue 1, Vol. 7, 2012.



October 2010 until Now

completed in January 2005

completed in August 2002



- W. Jatmiko, A. Azurat, Herry, A. Wibowo, H. Marihot, M. Wicaksana, I. Takagawa, K. Sekiyama, and T. Fukuda. Self-Organizing Urban Traffic Control Architecture with Swarm-Self Organizing Map in Jakarta: Signal Control System and Simulator, International Journal on Smart Sensing and Intelligent System, Vol. 3, No. 3, 2010.
- N. Anadito, R. Budiharto, Herry, and S. Yazid, *GridFTP-based Grid File System*, in Proceedings of 2010 International Conference on Advanced Computer Science and Information System, Bali, December 2010.
- Herry and H. Suhartanto, Algorithm of Parallel Supervised PNN Structure Determination and Its Implementation using Message Passing Interface, in Proceedings of 2009 International Conference on Advanced Computer Science and Information System, Jakarta, December 2009.

#### Awards

Finalist of UK ICT Pioneer Competition 2014 organised by Engineering and Physical Sciences Research Council (EPSRC) UK.

Scholarship of Postgraduate Industry Internship Program from The Scottish Informatics & Computer Science Alliance (SICSA) for internship in HP Labs Bristol, August-December 2013.

Scholarship from University of Edinburgh sponsored by **Hewlett Packard** Grant of HP Labs Innovation Research Program Award 2010-2013 for project: Planning for Autonomic Management of Computing Infrastructures (Grant Ref: CW219094).

Scholarship from The Association of International Education Japan (AIEJ) as visiting research student in Imaging Science and Engineering Laboratory, Tokyo Institute of Technology, Japan, 2002-2003.

#### **Skills**

Operating System: Linux, Windows, MacOS X

Programming Language: Java, Scala, OCaml, Ruby, JavaScript, C, Python, PHP, Bash Shell Script,

Nodeis, Matlab

System Configuration tools: Puppet, Ansible, SaltStack, LCFG, Nuri, Cisco Router

# **Working Experiences**

# School of Informatics, University of Edinburgh, UK

October 2010 – now

As a PhD research student with research project: Automated Planning for Cloud Service Configurations.

# Hewlett-Packard Laboratory, Bristol, UK

*August 2013 – January 2014* 

As an intern with projects: a survey on practical system configuration tools (a technical report); developing components for a prototype system configuration tool for Apache Hadoop, HP Automated Software, HP Cells, and Openstacks.

### School of Informatics, University of Edinburgh, UK

September 2011 – February 2014

As a teaching assistant for Introduction to Java Programming, Reasoning & Agents, and MOOC Automated Planning courses.

Faculty of Computer Science, University of Indonesia, Indonesia August 2009 – September 2010 As a lecturer for courses: Software Engineering, Software Quality Assurance, Software Project, Data

Structure & Algorithm, Management Process of Software Engineering, and

Management of Information Security.

As a researcher for projects: Data Management in Grid Computing, Traffic Control System, and Broadcasting System for Digital Television.

# Primas Global System, PT, Jakarta, Indonesia

January 2005 – August 2009

As a manager (last position).

Sadikun Niagamas Raya Group, PT, Jakarta, Indonesia

November 2003 – October 2004

As a system engineer and analyst.

Raytec, Co., Ltd., Tokyo, Japan

*February 2003 – August 2003* 

A system engineer (part-time)